# Kaiser DeKam



kaiserddekam@gmail.com

(507) 227-0436

3565 Tates Creek Rd Apt 49, Lexington, KY 40517

#### **Profile**

With a degree in Media Communications I am experienced in several facets of storytelling. With experience in writing, camera work, video and photo editing, as well as photojournalism and producing multi-formatted content. I have a large amount experience in the areas of in studio production as well as in the field filming. In terms of the video and design field, I am very familiar with a large array of applications such as Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere, and Final Cut Pro. When working with web content I also have experience with HTML and CSS and a solid understanding of AP style and in the early stages of iOS development.

## Experience

Man O' War Golf (Freelance) Videographer Lexington, KY Jun. 2014 - Present Working with several golf instructors we bring golf instructional materials to the web in a concise and more flexible medium. Each video runs between 3-6 minutes and covers a large variety of topics from instructional videos to promotional pieces. Technically they are all shot with up to 3 cameras and external lavalier microphones and edited with Final Cut Pro.

Volar Video Technical Support Lexington, KY Oct. 2013 - Present

Answering emails and over the phone inquires on technical support with online viewers as well as in the field broadcasters. Working along side broadcasters from the High School to the NCAA level I work with contacts across the country in monitoring and overseeing nationwide broadcasts. Other duties include testing equipment and software for in the field use.

MTV Networks Production Assistant Sioux Falls, SD Jun. 2012 - Dec. 2012

Traveled with documentary style crew working as a production assistant. Primarily carrying equipment, taking field notes, and assisting camera operators. Learned workflow and process of reality TV.

### Video Examples:

-Shot and Edited: "Promotional Video (Link)"

-Shot and Edited: "Instructional Video" (Link) - Company Channel

-Shot and Edited: "Abe Parker Short Documentary (Link)"

#### Education

Northwestern College Orange City, IA Media Communications 2009-2010

-Transferred-

Asbury University Wilmore, KY Media Communications (BA) 2010-2013

#### References

Adam Black

Team Leader <u>Volar Video</u> Adam.Black@volarvideo.com (855) 812-2740

Doug Walker

Professor Asbury Univ. Doug.Walker@asbury.edu N/A

Josh Braun

Co-Worker iHigh.com josh.Braun@ihigh.com (859) 533-1618